https://www.holonfoods.com/privacy-policy

Call:718-336-7758 Mail:info@holonfoods.com
Cart(0)
Items | total: $0.00 (0)
Your shopping cart is empty!
My Account
LoginRegister
Forget Password
Cart(0)
Items | total: $0.00 (0)
Your shopping cart is empty!
Purim Products
Hamentashen Purim CookiesPurim Gift BasketsChocolates For PurimCandies & Gums For PurimChips For PurimCookies & Wafers For PurimHoney For PurimDry Fruits & Nuts For PurimJuice Boxes For PurimGrape Juice For Purim
Kosher for Passover
Kosher Meat & Poultry For PassoverKosher Chicken for PassoverKosher Lamb For PassoverKosher Veal For PassoverKosher Marinated Meats for PassoverKosher Duck for PassoverKosher Beef for PassoverKosher Turkey for PassoverKosher Deli Department For PassoverHod Golan Kosher For PassoverPre Packed Meats Kosher For PassoverTirat Zvi Deli For PassoverFresh Deli Cold Cuts For PassoverHorseradish for PassoverRefrigerated Salads Kosher For PassoverKosher Dairy For PassoverButter & Margarine For PassoverCottage Cheese For PassoverCream Cheese For PassoverKosher Cheeses For PassoverSoft Cheese For PassoverYogurts For PassoverPudding For PassoverNon Dairy Creamers & Toppings For PassoverBeverages For PassoverCoffee & Tea For PassoverPowered Beverages and Creamers for PassoverJuices For PassoverJuice Boxes for PassoverKosher Parve Milk for PassoverBaby Food For PassoverCereals & Granola for PassoverBaking Items For PassoverBaking Chocolate For PassoverBaking Powder & Soda for PassoverCake Cookie & Muffin Mix for PassoverChocolate & Nut Butter Spreads For PassoverChocolate Chips & Sprinkles for PassoverCocoa Powder For PassoverDate Spread & Silian for PassoverFood Coloring & Extracts For PassoverHoney For PassoverJams & Preserves For PassoverJello & Pudding Mixes For PassoverSyrups For PassoverSugar, Flour & Starches For PassoverDry Fruits & Nuts For PassoverPackaged Seeds & Nuts For PassoverGourmet Dry Fruits & Nuts For PassoverBakery Cakes & Cupcakes For PassoverBake Master Bakery For PassoverPackaged Cakes & Muffins For PassoverSchicks Passover BakeryMatzah Crackers & Meals For PassoverChocolate Covered MatzahCake Meal for PassoverCrackers For PassoverMatzah Meal & Farfel for PassoverGeula Passover MaztahManischewitz Passover MaztahOsem Passover MaztahShumura Handmade MatzahStreits Passover MaztahYehuda Passover MaztahRice Pasta & Grains For PassoverCouscous & Quinoa For PassoverRice For PassoverPasta For PassoverPulses for PassoverSoup Spices & Cooking Mixes For PassoverSoup Consumme For PassoverMatzo Ball & Soup Mixes For PassoverPotato Mix For PassoverStuffing Mix For PassoverCoating Crumbs For PassoverGravy Mixes For PassoverCroutons for PassoverLiebers Spices For PassoverGefen Spices for PassoverPereg Spices for PassoverSalt For PassoverCooking Condiments & Sauces For PassoverBBQ Sauce For PassoverChinese Sauces & Marinades For PassoverCondiments for PassoverCooking Oil For PassoverDuck Sauces For PassoverHot & Chili Sauce For PassoverKetchup For PassoverMayonnaise For PassoverPasta & Pizza Sauce For PassoverSalad Dressing For PassoverSpecialty Sauces & Marinades for PassoverTahini for PassoverVinegar & Cooking Wine For PassoverCanned Fruits & Vegetables For PassoverCanned Vegetables For PassoverPickles & Cucumbers For PassoverCanned Olives For PassoverOriental Vegetables For PassoverCanned Tomatoes For PassoverFruit Cups for PassoverApplesauce for PassoverCanned Fruit For PassoverCookies Chips And SnacksCandies & Gum For PassoverChips For PassoverChocolate Candies For PassoverChocolate Covered MatzahCookies For PassoverCrackers for PassoverHalva for PassoverMacaroons For PassoverMarshmallows For PassoverRice Cakes for PassoverHousehold Products For PassoverCooking Bags & Baking Paper For PassoverCandles for PassoverKosher Dish Soap For PassoverSoap Pads & Cleanser for PassoverStove & Oven Cleaners for PassoverShabbos Hot Plate & Water Dispensers
Chanukah
Chanukah Candles & WicksChanukah MenorahCandle & Olive OilChocolate CoinsChanukah Gift BasketsSufganiyot DonutsLatkes and Pancake Mixes for ChanukahChanukah Treats
Rosh Hashanah
Cookies & PastriesCake LoafsHoliday ChallahsHoney & SilanRosh Hashanah GiftsRosh Hashanah Holiday Family Menu
Nine Days
Fresh Fruits & Vegetables
Fresh FruitOnionsTomatoesPotatoesFresh Herbs & GreensPeppersAssorted Veggies
Kosher Meats & Poultry
Fresh ChickenWhole & Cut Up Chicken-( Cubes & Strips )Chicken Parts- ( Legs, Thighs & Breasts )Skinless ChickenGround Chicken & BurgersMarinated ChickenFresh BeefBeef BonesBeef BrisketCubes & StripsDry Aged BeefGround Beef & BurgersPickled BeefSpecialty CutsSteaksRoastsFrozen DucksFresh LambFresh VealMarinated MeatsMarinated BurgersMarinated Meat CombosMarinated SteaksMarinated MeatsMarinated Shish KebabsSummer BBQ SamplersFresh TurkeyWhole TurkeysSplit & CutsGround Turkey & Burgers
Dairy Products
Dairy CreamersButter & MargarineCottage & Ricotta CheeseCream CheeseKosher CheeseImported CheesesYogurts & PuddingsImported Dairy SnacksLebenSoft Cheese SpreadSour CreamNon Dairy Products
Kosher Bakery
Bagels and BreadChallah BreadsPita Bread & WrapsCakes & LoafsCookies & Pastries
Kosher Grocery
BeveragesCoffeeTeaPowered MixesNon-Dairy MilkJuiceBaby FoodBreakfast GoodsGranolaCerealPancake & Waffle MixOatmeal & Hot CerealBaking ItemsBaking ChocolateCake Jello & Pudding MixesExtract Frosting & ToppingsFlour & StarchSugars & SweetenersJams & SpreadsChocolate Spreads & Peanut ButtersDate Spreads & SilianHoneyJams & PreservesSyrupsCanned GoodsApplesauceCanned Beans & Chick PeasCanned FruitsCanned OlivesCanned VegetablesCanned TomatoesJarred VegetablesOriental VegetablesPickles & CucumbersSauces & MarinadesBBQ SauceBeef & Chicken MarinatesDuck SaucesPasta & Pizza SauceSalsa Dips & Taco SaucesSoy & Teriyaki SauceDressing Vinegars & OilsCooking Wines & VinegarsCooking Oils & SprayKetchup Mayo & MustardSalad DressingsTahini & AmbaSoup Spices & Cooking MixesBread & Coating CrumbsGravy MixesInstant SoupSoup ConsumesMatzo Ball & Soup MixesPotato & Latkes MixesStuffing MixesPereg SpicesLiebers SpicesSaltPasta & GrainsCouscous & QuinoaDry Beans & PulsesEgg NoodlesGluten Free PastaOriental Noodles & PastaPastasRicesTaco ShellsSnack FoodsChips and PopcornBamba & BissliBread Sticks & Flat BreadsCookiesCrackersRice CakesTea BiscuitsWafersCandies & ChocolatesChocolate Bars and CandiesElite Chocolates & CandyHalvaKlik ChocolatesAssorted Candies & SnacksMarshmallowsMentos Gum & CandiesMike & Ike CandiesMust Gum & CandiesPaskesz CandiesPackaged Nuts & SeedsGourmet Dry Fruits & Nuts
WHOLESALE DEPT
Kosher Deli Counter
Fresh Cold CutsPrepacked Deli MeatDeli Salads & SpreadsHummus & TehiniMediterranean SaladsSalsa & GuacamoleHorseradishes & Relish
New
Shabbos Boxes
Frozen Foods
Dough & PastriesFrozen Appetizers & PizzaPizza & Pizza BagelsFrozen hor doeuvresFrench Fries & Onion RingsFrozen Bourekas & AppetizersFrozen Fruits & VeggiesFrozen FruitsFrozen SpicesBodek Frozen VegetablesYerek Frozen VegetablesFrozen VegetablesFrozen Fish & VegetarianGefilte FishFish FilletsVegetarian Burgers & PattiesFrozen Meat & Poultry ProductsFrozen Livers & FatChicken Nuggets & WingsFalafel Balls
Kosher Household
Laundry Care & DetergentsCooking & Baking PaperImported Body ProductsShampoo & ConditionersHair Lotions & Styling CreamsBody CareKosher Dish Washing SoapStove & Oven CleanersSoap Pads & CleanserShabbos Candles & AccessoriesCandle HoldersShabbos Hot Plate & Water Dispensers
Israeli Products
PASSOVER FOODSKosher For Passover BeefGROCERYGROCERIESSOUP MIXESOILS & VINEGARSSAUCES & DRESSINGSSPREADS & JAMSTUNA & SARDINESINSTANT MEALSRICES & BEANSCANNED FOODSCOFFEE & TEADRINKS & JUICESPICKLES & OLIVESSNACKSSPICES & SEASONINGSBABY FOODSSPREADSNUTS, SEEDS, & DRY FRUITSCHOCOLATE CANDY & GUMCHOCOLATECANDYGUMMEATSBEEFVEALLAMBCHICKENTURKEYBAKERYCOOKIESCAKESBREADSCAKE MIXES & FILLINGSDAIRY PRODUCTSMILLERSGOLANSTRAUSSTNUVACHEESESYOGURTHOUSEHOLDDETERGENTCLEANING PRODUCTSCANDLESGEL, SHAMPOO, & BEAUTY PRODUCTSDELIFROZEN FOODSISRAELI MUSIC CD'STELEPHONE CARDSPurim ProductsHamentashen Purim Cookies
Toggle navigation
PASSOVER FOODS
Kosher For Passo...
GROCERY
GROCERIES
SOUP MIXES
OILS & VINEGARS
SAUCES & DRESSIN...
SPREADS & JAMS
TUNA & SARDINES
INSTANT MEALS
RICES & BEANS
CANNED FOODS
COFFEE & TEA
DRINKS & JUICES
PICKLES & OLIVES
SNACKS
SPICES & SEASONI...
BABY FOODS
SPREADS
NUTS, SEEDS, & D...
SNACKS
CHOCOLATE CANDY & GUM
CHOCOLATE
CANDY
GUM
COFFEE & TEA
DRINKS & JUICES
SPICES & SEASONINGS
Search
Home  Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We take your privacy seriously.
Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.
What This Privacy Policy Covers:
This Privacy Policy covers our site treatment of personally identifiable information that our site collects when you are on it, and when you use our site services.
This policy also covers our site treatment of any personally identifiable information that our business partners share with us or that we may collect on a partner's site.
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that our site does not own or control, or to people that our site does not employ or manage
Information Collection and Use
Our site collects personally identifiable information when you register for your account, or when you submit an order.
When you register with us, we ask for your name, email address, mailing address, telephone, and credit card information. Once you register with us and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookies information and the page you requested.
We use information for three general purposes:
To customize the content you see.
To fulfill your requests for certain products and services.
To contact you about specials and new products.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.
Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information and Preferences
We give you the ability to edit your account information and preferences at any time after logging in, including whether you want us to contact you about specials and new products.
You may request deletion of your account by email, verifying your password and confirming your choice to terminate the account.
Security
Your account information is password-protected for your privacy and security.
In certain areas we use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
Featured Products
Platinum jojoba hair wax
Picnic Red S’chug
Rosemarie split chocolate bar
Pereg hot red paprika with oil
DEPARTMENTS
Purim Products Hamentashen Purim CookiesPurim Gift BasketsChocolates For PurimCandies & Gums For PurimChips For PurimCookies & Wafers For PurimHoney For PurimDry Fruits & Nuts For PurimJuice Boxes For PurimGrape Juice For PurimKosher for Passover Kosher Meat & Poultry For PassoverKosher Chicken for PassoverKosher Lamb For PassoverKosher Veal For PassoverKosher Marinated Meats for PassoverKosher Beef for PassoverKosher Turkey for PassoverKosher Deli Department For PassoverHod Golan Kosher For PassoverPre Packed Meats Kosher For PassoverTirat Zvi Deli For PassoverFresh Deli Cold Cuts For PassoverHorseradish for PassoverRefrigerated Salads Kosher For PassoverKosher Dairy For PassoverButter & Margarine For PassoverCottage Cheese For PassoverCream Cheese For PassoverKosher Cheeses For PassoverSoft Cheese For PassoverYogurts For PassoverPudding For PassoverNon Dairy Creamers & Toppings For PassoverBeverages For PassoverCoffee & Tea For PassoverJuices For PassoverJuice Boxes for PassoverKosher Parve Milk for PassoverBaby Food For PassoverCereals & Granola for PassoverBaking Items For PassoverBaking Chocolate For PassoverBaking Powder & Soda for PassoverCake Cookie & Muffin Mix for PassoverChocolate & Nut Butter Spreads For PassoverChocolate Chips & Sprinkles for PassoverCocoa Powder For PassoverDate Spread & Silian for PassoverFood Coloring & Extracts For PassoverHoney For PassoverJams & Preserves For PassoverJello & Pudding Mixes For PassoverSyrups For PassoverSugar, Flour & Starches For PassoverDry Fruits & Nuts For PassoverPackaged Seeds & Nuts For PassoverGourmet Dry Fruits & Nuts For PassoverBakery Cakes & Cupcakes For PassoverBake Master Bakery For PassoverPackaged Cakes & Muffins For PassoverSchicks Passover BakeryMatzah Crackers & Meals For PassoverChocolate Covered MatzahCake Meal for PassoverCrackers For PassoverMatzah Meal & Farfel for PassoverManischewitz Passover MaztahOsem Passover MaztahShumura Handmade MatzahStreits Passover MaztahYehuda Passover MaztahRice Pasta & Grains For PassoverCouscous & Quinoa For PassoverRice For PassoverPulses for PassoverSoup Spices & Cooking Mixes For PassoverSoup Consumme For PassoverMatzo Ball & Soup Mixes For PassoverPotato Mix For PassoverStuffing Mix For PassoverCoating Crumbs For PassoverGravy Mixes For PassoverLiebers Spices For PassoverPereg Spices for PassoverSalt For PassoverCooking Condiments & Sauces For PassoverBBQ Sauce For PassoverChinese Sauces & Marinades For PassoverCondiments for PassoverCooking Oil For PassoverDuck Sauces For PassoverHot & Chili Sauce For PassoverKetchup For PassoverMayonnaise For PassoverPasta & Pizza Sauce For PassoverSalad Dressing For PassoverSpecialty Sauces & Marinades for PassoverTahini for PassoverVinegar & Cooking Wine For PassoverCanned Fruits & Vegetables For PassoverCanned Vegetables For PassoverPickles & Cucumbers For PassoverCanned Olives For PassoverOriental Vegetables For PassoverCanned Tomatoes For PassoverFruit Cups for PassoverApplesauce for PassoverCanned Fruit For PassoverCookies Chips And SnacksCandies & Gum For PassoverChips For PassoverChocolate Candies For PassoverCookies For PassoverHalva for PassoverMacaroons For PassoverMarshmallows For PassoverRice Cakes for PassoverHousehold Products For PassoverCooking Bags & Baking Paper For PassoverCandles for PassoverSoap Pads & Cleanser for PassoverStove & Oven Cleaners for PassoverChanukah Chanukah Candles & WicksChanukah MenorahChocolate CoinsChanukah Gift BasketsSufganiyot DonutsLatkes and Pancake Mixes for ChanukahRosh Hashanah Cookies & PastriesCake LoafsHoliday ChallahsHoney & SilanRosh Hashanah GiftsRosh Hashanah Holiday Family MenuNine Days Fresh Fruits & Vegetables Fresh FruitOnionsTomatoesPotatoesFresh Herbs & GreensPeppersAssorted VeggiesKosher Meats & Poultry Fresh ChickenWhole & Cut Up Chicken-( Cubes & Strips )Chicken Parts- ( Legs, Thighs & Breasts )Skinless ChickenGround Chicken & BurgersMarinated ChickenFresh BeefBeef BonesBeef BrisketDry Aged BeefGround Beef & BurgersPickled BeefSpecialty CutsRoastsFresh LambFresh VealMarinated MeatsMarinated BurgersMarinated Meat CombosMarinated SteaksMarinated Shish KebabsSummer BBQ SamplersFresh TurkeyWhole TurkeysSplit & CutsGround Turkey & BurgersDairy Products Dairy CreamersButter & MargarineCottage & Ricotta CheeseCream CheeseKosher CheeseYogurts & PuddingsImported Dairy SnacksLebenSoft Cheese SpreadSour CreamNon Dairy ProductsKosher Bakery Bagels and BreadChallah BreadsPita Bread & WrapsCakes & LoafsKosher Grocery BeveragesCoffeeTeaPowered MixesNon-Dairy MilkJuiceBaby FoodBreakfast GoodsGranolaCerealPancake & Waffle MixOatmeal & Hot CerealBaking ItemsBaking ChocolateCake Jello & Pudding MixesExtract Frosting & ToppingsFlour & StarchSugars & SweetenersJams & SpreadsChocolate Spreads & Peanut ButtersDate Spreads & SilianHoneyJams & PreservesSyrupsCanned GoodsApplesauceCanned Beans & Chick PeasCanned FruitsCanned OlivesCanned VegetablesCanned TomatoesJarred VegetablesOriental VegetablesPickles & CucumbersSauces & MarinadesBBQ SauceBeef & Chicken MarinatesDuck SaucesPasta & Pizza SauceSalsa Dips & Taco SaucesSoy & Teriyaki SauceDressing Vinegars & OilsCooking Wines & VinegarsCooking Oils & SprayKetchup Mayo & MustardSalad DressingsTahini & AmbaSoup Spices & Cooking MixesBread & Coating CrumbsGravy MixesInstant SoupSoup ConsumesMatzo Ball & Soup MixesPotato & Latkes MixesPereg SpicesLiebers SpicesSaltPasta & GrainsCouscous & QuinoaDry Beans & PulsesEgg NoodlesOriental Noodles & PastaPastasRicesTaco ShellsSnack FoodsChips and PopcornBamba & BissliBread Sticks & Flat BreadsCrackersRice CakesTea BiscuitsWafersCandies & ChocolatesChocolate Bars and CandiesElite Chocolates & CandyHalvaKlik ChocolatesAssorted Candies & SnacksMarshmallowsMentos Gum & CandiesMike & Ike CandiesMust Gum & CandiesPaskesz CandiesPackaged Nuts & SeedsGourmet Dry Fruits & NutsWHOLESALE DEPT Kosher Deli Counter Fresh Cold CutsPrepacked Deli MeatDeli Salads & SpreadsHummus & TehiniMediterranean SaladsSalsa & GuacamoleHorseradishes & RelishNew Shabbos BoxesFrozen Foods Frozen Appetizers & PizzaPizza & Pizza BagelsFrozen hor doeuvresFrench Fries & Onion RingsFrozen Bourekas & AppetizersFrozen Fruits & VeggiesFrozen SpicesBodek Frozen VegetablesYerek Frozen VegetablesFrozen VegetablesFrozen Fish & VegetarianFish FilletsVegetarian Burgers & PattiesFrozen Meat & Poultry ProductsChicken Nuggets & WingsFalafel BallsKosher Household Laundry Care & DetergentsCooking & Baking PaperImported Body ProductsShampoo & ConditionersHair Lotions & Styling CreamsBody CareKosher Dish Washing SoapStove & Oven CleanersShabbos Candles & AccessoriesCandle HoldersIsraeli Products PASSOVER FOODSGROCERYGROCERIESSOUP MIXESOILS & VINEGARSSAUCES & DRESSINGSSPREADS & JAMSTUNA & SARDINESINSTANT MEALSRICES & BEANSCANNED FOODSCOFFEE & TEADRINKS & JUICESPICKLES & OLIVESSNACKSSPICES & SEASONINGSBABY FOODSSPREADSNUTS, SEEDS, & DRY FRUITSCHOCOLATE CANDY & GUMCHOCOLATECANDYGUMMEATSBEEFLAMBCHICKENTURKEYBAKERYCOOKIESCAKESCAKE MIXES & FILLINGSDAIRY PRODUCTSMILLERSSTRAUSSTNUVACHEESESHOUSEHOLDDETERGENTCLEANING PRODUCTSCANDLESGEL, SHAMPOO, & BEAUTY PRODUCTSDELIFROZEN FOODSTELEPHONE CARDSPurim ProductsHamentashen Purim Cookies
Latest Items
NEWSLETTER
SUBSCRIBE
Contact Us
Holon Foods 527 Kings HwyBrooklyn, NY 11223  USACall: 718-336-7758 info@holonfoods.com
Other Links
Our Policy
Advanced Search
Shipping Policy
Terms and Conditions
Information
Tell A Friend
About Us
View Cart
By using this website, you agree to our use of cookies. We use cookies to provide you with a great experience and to help our website run effectively. More info.
Accept Cookie
×
Www.holonfoods.com Links Code Selection
Your Link Code Text
PLEASE NOTE: Do not change any of the link code when you install it in your pages!
Close
×Close
×
Please Select from and to Date to Export
From:
To:
